Yes one second welcome back to You Have Dress
2.0, welcome all of you once again
friends, in this video we are going to talk about
CSC's insurance service,
in this video we are going to tell you about how to do CSC's ICC
Lombard's third party two wheeler
insurance,
so
I want to tell you one thing here,
if you are new and want to do insurance for your CSC
center, then the easiest and simplest
way of
insurance here is that you get it from ICC Lombard,
so I would prefer you that
whenever you do any CSC
insurance, first go to ICC,
so if you want to go to any other website you
can go there too, it will be a little
cheaper maybe, but generally the
price of all is shown here,
third party
insurance of 1 wheeler, so let me show you here, I don't
waste much time, so
now I am taking you to the system
and I will tell you how you have to
press here, first of all you have to do
insurance in your digital service portal  You will have to
come to the Wale tab and you will have to click on Motor Third Party
here, in the last
you will get the option of ICC Lombard here,
click on it, click on it, as soon as
you click, the new tab will open,
after that your details will be uploaded here,
you can see, everything will be uploaded
here, after that as soon as you
come here, suppose you have to insure your new bike or
new vehicle here, then
you can do that too, so see below there are two
options, if you do it on New Wale and on To
Player you will do Third Party, so
see this, by clicking on this you will click on Get, then your
details will
open like this, you can see by
writing New here and you can fill
everything here, then after that you
can fill the station number, so I will tell you here
how you have to do it for the third
party, like if you have to do it for the old bike, then
how to do it,
then what you have to do is you will have to
go to Home, then you will get the option of Back here,
click on it, Two
Wheeler Third Party, click on
Renwal wala and Fresh Detail wala  Both will be
selected, then click on Get here,
as you will click on it,
now you will see here that the new option is
not there, so here the registration number is there,
so here you have to enter the registration number
and click on Get RTO details,
so I will enter it here, after that
you will click on Get RTO here and I will
show you how it comes to you, so let
me read it first, after that I will
show it to you,
friends, here I have filled it, we will get it,
see all the details are
filled here automatically and after that you do
not have to do anything here, here
you will see below, there is already a hall here and
see, here the accident tax will be there, so
when you come, it may
not be like this, then you will see no here and yes
here, so you have to change it here
and you will see, after that you will
click on Get here, then 843 will
come here, see I had done this myself, it was coming here,
when you come for the first time,
click in this way and here the
first one will be no and the second one will be yes, so
1433 will be charged, what happens in this is that you will also
do it and the person who has an accident will
also do it, so in this way what you have to do is
first you have to do yes, second no,
if you want to make the person the cheapest then after doing it in
this way you have to click on next here, then
as you click,
see all the details will be there, if
you want to set a nominee here then you
can also add nominees from here, if you do
not want to do it then you can remove it,
see after that if you
add here then their nominees' data has to be created
further, after that all these
details have to be done here, so no one does this quickly,
after that you will leave it here, now what about this,
in such details, it is very
important here that you have to do
KYC, those who have
come here for insurance, in whose name the
vehicle is, do it for them here, so
what you have to do for that, you have to
take a PAN card and
enter the PAN card number here in the PAN card and
enter their database here, so see here, for example, I have my  After
entering the PAN card, I will enter the
date of birth here and
as soon as you come to the date of birth,
you have to know a little bit about it,
click on it and go up while holding it, then release it,
then it will go here, see you have to do it
slowly, otherwise what will happen is that
you will be able to do it quickly, so slowly take
it up and as soon as it
comes down and your year which comes here, you will
select it, see I am 1992 by
selecting it here, okay, in this way,
then you select the name and date and
submit it, then your details will be
filled here completely, yes, the
details in the PAN card will come from there, then
after that, the declaration here is here, you have to
leave it like this, after that you have to
click on proceed here, if
something happens then this will be considered cancelled, so
this is all the things, so if you have
any problem here, then you can write that too,
or else you will press no and
submit it, then see all the details will be
filed here, after that what you will have to do is that
you will enter your city here  If the city has to be created, then
you will fill in its city here, then after the city, you
must fill in the email ID and the mobile number as well. It is
not necessary for you to leave out the rest of the things that are not stars, the
rest of the mandatory things have to be filled in,
star by star, it will be good to do that,
after that click generate here, then
your amount will be added, how much
your amount will be charged here, see 843 is going here,
its policy number will also be added,
after that you have to accept and click on buynote here,
friends, this is all you have to do,
after that as you click on bin,
it will go to the wallet of your digital service portal
for payment, if there is
no payment in your account, then the
code will come here in this way, in a very
simple way, very easy, you will do the
insurance here within just 10 minutes
and you just have to make the payment in the end,
as soon as you make the payment,
you will get a PF file, you
can download it and give it to the customer by putting your stamp,
yes, your customer stamp must be affixed here
so that it can be known here that you have
It has been insured here from this CCC centre,
friends, that's all you have to do,
after that you will copy it and
his insurance will be deducted and yours will also be
deducted here and the commission you have will be
added to your wallet later, so
friends, in this way you can do
third party insurance of two wheeler in CSC, I
hope you liked the video, you must have found it
informative, secondly like the
video and now if you have any
other problem,
you can ask that also in the comment and if you have
come to the channel for the first time and have not subscribed to the channel yet, then please please do
subscribe because I
bring genuine videos in the same way,
you can watch them here, so
friends, we will meet again in the next video, till then
take care bye